It's not a time to see how good you are, it's a time to see how much energy you can generate.
Ishimori, you're going through something, aren't you? But it's good that you can cry. If you can cry, it means you can understand the feelings of those who can cry.
All 11 members of the 3rd term students will work together to make the van, and depending on how well it turns out, it will determine whether or not we make a music video.
And depending on how it turns out, we will make a music video or not. We will all say, "We really did it!
I want to do my best so that we can say, "Wow, aren't we amazing?
We want to do our best so that we can give a great performance!
There's a lot of these things that happen.
I mean, there's going to be days when we're doing this performance and things are happening.
There are days when someone is going through a hard time.
I know the members have the feeling to be hard together at that time, but
To always pull them up on stage.
So we're not going to be hard together.
Then we will give twice the power
Nishimori will be ready to go
The important thing is to do the best you can do today
I told you about the scale
Don't suddenly say it's no good because it's not where I want it to be
I've already said enough.
We're going to push it.
Well then, let's go.
I'm Nagisa Kojima, Sakurazaka 46 third term student.
We have been working together for the past month, all 11 of us, to make the third term van.
Whenever someone had a hard time or was sad during practice, we all supported each other.
Today, with the teamwork we have built up so far
We will deliver the best performance we can now with the 11 of us united in one heart.
Thank you very much.
Hey!
I was watching the Yadama Shimahore video.
That's no way to wake me up.
I missed everything.
I missed the whole thing and today is over
Kakumembo's bathroom
why couldn't I do that?
Why did you yawn all the time?
What about you?
Hey!
What a bold laugh
I bet you don't even know what it means to someone else
I've been playing games all my life
Someday I'll get to dance
Where did you go?
why do you want that kind of love
Wait a minute, wait a minute
It was in this hole, wasn't it?
I couldn't make it last my whole life.
I'm the only one
I'll suppress my feelings
Even if I'm found out, even if I'm believed
Even if you tell me I can't do it
From now on, I'm the next one
You can't make it happen
Even if they find out, even if they believe you
Even if you stop me...
I understand.
You'll change your mind, but you'll never be sorry.
God... what?
What can't you do?
Disinfect the place.
This time I don't give a shit.
Yes, sir.
It was a mistake... not doing anything behind the scenes.
I don't know what I was thinking.
What was I supposed to do with my life?
What are we doing here?
We can play.
Somebody tell me what we're doing here.
Some things have to change.
Suddenly, it's so one-sided.
I don't trust the left side.
Munster, what if there's something wrong?
Daikichi 16 is to blame.
If you want to do it one more time...
Just give me one more chance.
Munster, what if it had happened?
We didn't even need Missel.
I was worried about being young.
I thought it was great.
That's just the way it was in my old town.
You'll be sorry.
Why don't you take enough?
Hundred thousand points
Hey!
He's home. I saw him this morning. Let me help you.
I don't know what's wrong with you guys.
What's wrong with this place?
I want to know what's wrong with me.
I'm sure I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
As for the performance, I've been watching since the training camp, and I feel that everyone's ability is improving day by day.
I think we are getting closer to the situation where we can stand on the stage.
I think we are getting close to being on stage, and I think we need to show what we need to do to get there.
I need to be seen and I need to be shown.
Thank you for your hard work
It's just for a moment.It's a moment.
Some people work hard for months to create a moment.
Some people say they have achieved what they set out to do.
while others say, "I could have done more...".
I'm sure there are a lot of emotions.
I think it's finally time to move up to the next stage
I think we are finally starting to feel that it is okay to go up to the stage.
On February 15, the next Sakurazaka single will be released!
This is our next project!
This will be the first original song by a third term student.
What kind of work can everyone do?
I hope that we can unite our hearts one more time and create a great piece of work!
Thank you very much for your hard work!
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
The big thing is that I could imagine a picture of the girls standing on the stage, even if I look at it as Sakurazaka.
In other words, I think it was well done.
The seniors are waiting for you to come, and the 3rd term students are joining us because they like Sakurazaka and the group, so I think we are going to be a very strong team.
They must have been very nervous.
I was nervous but I personally thought it was a great show.
I think Ri-chan Yajima was chosen by lot to be the center of the group, but sometimes the center or other special positions can be a bit lonely, and there are moments when you have to fight alone.
I thought it was really nice that Ri-chan Yajima asked the other members to join her when she was practicing by herself, and I thought that was very important.
I thought it was very important, and after watching this show, I felt that the 3rd term students of Sakurazaka 46 will become a very special team and people, so let's keep up the good work.
Yes, I'm sorry. I'm sorry for going on for so long.
Thank you very much.
Thanks to the teachers, I am learning new things and my heart is getting stronger and stronger.
What was it?
I was so happy to receive compliments at my first lesson after the camp.
I didn't hate dancing even though it was obvious that I wasn't as good as everyone else.
I am a slower learner than others, so I am really causing a lot of trouble.
But they were still polite and didn't give up on me, which made me feel very relieved.
I am sure I will cause you a lot of trouble, but I will do my best.
I will do my best.
There were many things I couldn't do, and when I went to ask the teacher about them, she carefully explained them to me and danced with me many times until I could do them.
He never gave up on me.
Wait for me.
As Ms. Mae-san said, there were many times when I felt lonely, but the teachers probably understood that, too.
So I was very happy to know that they were warmly watching my lessons without forcing me to interfere too much.
I will do my best from now on.
Thank you all.
Thank you very much.
I really think the real work starts now, so let's work hard from now on so we don't get burnt out.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
Nagi Kojima
Yes, thank you very much.
Mizuki Nakajima
Yes
Target Beauty Time Jai
Ishimori
Murayama Beauty
Sorashi Oda
Emperor
And number 22, Tora Okayama
With the two of you in my heart
you.
Nice to meet you all.
Like this
You're the oldest of the third-term students.
I'll do my best to be your boss.
My name is Sakurazuka46.
National tour final performance at Tokyo Dome
Welcome!
Thank you for your support for the past 7 years!
We hope to bring the quality of our performance to the level that we can perform in front of the audience!
On and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on!
The seniors I saw yesterday are going to go ahead of us.
We all have to catch up with them even if we try our best.
When the members of Sakurazuka have to learn the choreography, they learn it all in three hours.
They learn it all in three hours.
They're just singing. They're just moving their mouths.
It looks like they're just moving their mouths.
That doesn't convey the world of the song at all.
You have to deliver it, so you have to deliver it.
Your job is to deliver the song.
You can see it yourself, can't you?
I can't dance at all.
I'm really the best dancer in the group.
You'll check with me and you'll learn it.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
How's it going?
Yo! That was fast!
One, two, three, four, that's it!
It's very important to practice without giving up!
Whenever one of us gets a compliment, we feel like we have to take it.
It's like you have to be happy.
From my point of view, Miyu is a very perfect person.
And yet, you lack self-confidence.
I want to have confidence in myself!
So I'm sure you're carrying that on your shoulders.
You're the oldest.
I'm sure she's thinking, "I'm the oldest, I have to do it.
Bon appétit!
Looks so delicious!
Delicious, so delicious!
The good part was that everyone's eyes, you know, were alive!
If you do it, you will grow.
I hope that what you have done will take shape when you get on stage.
We will continue to push you until the very last minute so that what you have done will take shape when you stand on the stage.
Please be aware that today is not the end, but the beginning.
May I?
Yes, sir!Yes!
Yes, that means 10,000!
Yes, 10,000 Reacher!
Wow, I wonder why it's me, I'm so sorry.
Mukai-chan, that's great!
You were not at the camp, but you did great!
I'm doing my best to make up for everyone's hard work, and I'm really trying to invite my regrets and do my best.
I used to like being by myself, but now I feel like I have a group of friends, which makes me happy.
I feel like I can go a little further, so I hope that we can show our team power one more time!
Yappaso to Sakurazaka!
I know that there will be some happenings in this performance, and there will be days when someone will be in pain, but I want to make sure that the members will pull each other up on stage.
We will do our best!
The 11 of us will unite our hearts and deliver the best performance we can now.
I hope that you will unite your hearts once again and create a wonderful original song for the first time as a 3rd term student.
Happy New Year! I look forward to working with you again this year.
As the year comes to a close, I'm ready to do my best in everything.
I hope to do my best in everything I do.
In 2023, the production of the music for the third term is finally in full swing.
I would like to know what you would like to show in this music video, how it came about, and what you would like to do with it.
I would like to make the theme of the music video about how to break out of your shell and blossom from loneliness.
Toward the end of the music video, it seems that the audience is becoming more and more idolized.
I think it would be better to have a movement that shows a little more of your feelings, but with a little more gusto.
But I don't think it's enough to make the audience feel like they're being gung-ho, so I think it would be better to have them dance very gung-ho.
Please practice so much that even if you dance with a lot of gusto, you won't skip a beat.
I'm in a bit of pain right now, but I can see hope.
The theme of the third term students is that we are becoming more and more like a team.
I hope you can express your feelings like I am fighting against loneliness.
This is the first music video for the third term students.
It was the first music video for a third-term student, and the theme of the song was the most challenging.
I think it's a good thing that we can do it because we're third-term students.
I don't think it's very rare to get a separate song for each term.
I really hope they take good care of it.
I think the music video of this moment is something that can only be made at this time.
Congratulations!
Congratulations on turning 17 and 21!
I don't feel like a 21-year-old.
I'll do my best to be your big sister.
Everyone calls me a baby.
It hurts to be a baby.
I'll do my best to support everyone
I will do my best to be a supportive person.
The most important thing for us 3rd term students is to be polite to our seniors and to surpass them.
If the next group is weaker than us, the group will become weaker and weaker.
It's not like that. The 3rd term students who came into the group are better than us.
If we want to be better than them, then we should be more than them.
If you can play the part, if you can listen to your feelings, if you can jump over the pretense, we'll be happy.
If we can show our technique in this way, I think Murayama's goodness will disappear.
I want you to be aware that it's not the same no matter who does it, but only what I can do because it was me.
From now on, it's not about who we are to be seen, but who we are to show, because it's our work.
So let's make the best of ourselves!
Well, that's all for today, thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Erotic Baisers, let's go for it!
Weee!
We are...
We're always a work in progress.
Maybe...
We may not have all the answers
But
We'll keep running
I'm starting to like you, even though you're sad
It might be easier if I just give up
But I'll never be the one to say it
The weather and my feelings are the same
I'll remain your friend
I'll stay a friend inside of my empty heart, taking shelter from the rain, waiting for the sun to break through the clouds.
I'll wait here for the sun
Summy darling, from the rain, from afar
I love you so much
Even though it won't change even if I look up
Somewhere there's a rainbow
I can't stop hoping
Come on, look at it
It makes me sad
When will it come?
I can't unfold it
I have an umbrella
Right now
To see you
No matter what the time
I believe that love is unending and eternal